http://www.blankparkzoo.com/privacy-policy/

Hours
Open Daily, 10 a.m. - 4 p.m.
Closed Nov 26, Dec 24, 25 & Jan 1
View All Rates ›
Directions
Tickets
Open Daily, 10 a.m. - 4 p.m.
Research
Plant.Grow.Fly.
Adopt an Animal
Zoo Kids Inc.
Research
Plant.Grow.Fly.
Adopt an Animal
Zoo Kids Inc.
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY/TERMS OF USE:
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy explains the information we collect when you visit our site, how we collect it, how we use it, and how we protect it. This policy does not apply to offline activities. Your use of our site constitutes your agreement to the terms of this policy. From time to time, we may modify this policy, so please review it periodically for changes. Your continued use after a modification indicates your agreement to the modified terms.
Anonymous Information
We may collect anonymous information about your use of our site and aggregate this anonymous information for statistical analysis.  For instance, we may use it to determine usage patterns so we know which parts of our site are most popular.  Examples of the type of anonymous information we collect and how it is collected are:
Cookies: a small text file that may be used to collect information about your activity on our site. You may set your browser to block cookies, but doing so may prevent you from taking advantage of certain features of our site.
Internet Tags: provide information about your browser (e.g., Microsoft Internet Explorer), operating system (e.g., Windows), Internet service provider (e.g., Mediacom), and similar information.
IP Addresses: a number assigned to your computer by a Web server when you are on the Internet; we might use IP address information to determine the number of users who have visited a specific area of our site.  Please note we could use this information to identify you if necessary to comply with legal requirements or for security issues.
Personally Identifiable Information
What is Personally Identifiable Information?  Personally Identifiable Information ("Your Information") includes information such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, street address, credit card number and credit card expiration date.
How We Collect Your Information.  We collect Your Information only when you voluntarily provide it to us on our site, such as during an online transaction to purchase products, make donations, sign up to receive emails, become a member or complete registrations.  You may need to provide Your Information to participate in certain programs and activities or receive certain services or offers.  Please note that when you purchase some items offered on our site, you must provide Your Information to a third-party service provider on its Web site.  In these circumstances, you will know that you are on another Web site because the URL will change.  You should read the privacy policy of the third-party site before providing Your Information.
How We Use Your Information.  We will use Your Information for the purpose for which you give it to us (e.g., to complete an online purchase, donation, membership, or program registration). We may use Your Information to send you occasional postal and/or electronic mailings about the Blank Park Zoo and programs that we think interest you.  We also may use Your Information to send you occasional postal and/or electronic mailings about third parties whose information or services we think may be of interest to you.
Your Ability to Choose.  You may "opt out" of receiving marketing information that we send to you by unsubscribing to the mailing list, following instructions in the applicable information sent to you, or by contacting us by e-mail to info@blankparkzoo.com, or by calling 515-974-2584.
How We Share Your Information. We may share Your Information with third parties that perform services for the Blank Park Zoo, such as providing technology services, conducting membership mailings or providing postal and electronic mailing platforms and services. We also reserve the right to disclose Your Information in circumstances that we deem necessary or appropriate, such as to respond to legal process or request from a governmental agency, security reasons or similar situations.
Please note that if you become a member through our site, Your Information may be shared with third parties (e.g., other nonprofit organizations) whose information or services we think may be of interest to you. These third parties may wish to communicate with you by regular mail or email or share your information with others. If you want to unsubscribe, please email us at info@blankparkzoo.org, or call 515-974-2584.
Please note that if you purchase through our site a combination membership with Living History Farms and/or the Science Center of Iowa, we will share Your Information with those organizations and your purchase constitutes acceptance of the privacy policies and terms of use for the websites operated by those organizations. See http://www.livinghistoryfarms.org or http://www.sciowa.org for more information.
Donor Privacy Policy & Recognition
The Blank Park Zoo Foundation will not sell, trade or share a donor's personal information with anyone else or send donor mailings on behalf of other organizations.
If you donate funds to the Blank Park Zoo Foundation, Inc. through our site, we may print your name on signage, literature and other uses. If you wish to give anonymously, you can arrange this through our development office at 515-974-2589.
Children under the Age of 13
Children under the age of 13 are welcome to use and enjoy our site. The e-mail, newsletter, participation in the blogs, forums, registration, shopping and other offers on the site; however, are intended only for audiences age 13 and older. Please do not give us your name, e-mail address or any other information if you are under the age of 13. If we learn that we have received this information from a child under 13, we will immediately delete the information. Please e-mail us at info@blankparkzoo.com, or call 515-974-2527 if you have reason to believe we have received information from a child under the age of 13, and we will immediately delete the information.
Security
We strive to keep Your Information secure and safeguard it from unauthorized access by using “Secure Socket Layer” encryption to protect credit card numbers, firewalls to protect our servers, and virus/intrusion detection software. However, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so keep in mind that you provide Your Information at your own risk.
Third Party Software
This site may contain third party software, such as YouTube video players, as a convenience. This privacy policy does not cover use of this third party software.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our Site may include links to other Web sites that may be of interest to you.  Any links are provided only as a convenience and do not imply any endorsement of another site.  Be sure to read the privacy policies on other Web sites.
Transfer to the United States
If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States and that by providing Your Information, you consent to this transfer and storage of the data in the United States.
Forums and Blogs
We wish to encourage the open exchange of information through our site. We do not endorse or guaranty the accuracy of any posting. If you participate in any Blog or any forum on the website, you give us your permission to use these statements, your name and all other information you provide for any purpose. We are not responsible for the use of this information by others.
Review and Correction
If you would like to review or correct the information that you provided to us (or if you have comments or questions about our site), you can contact us at 515-974-2584.
REFUND POLICY:
Online Gift Shop: All purchases are final from the online gift shop. If a product is found to be defective, The Blank Park Zoo Foundation, Inc. will, at its option, replace the item or refund the credit card. All shipping charges related to the return of the product are the responsibility of the purchaser.
Membership Purchase: Because a temporary membership pass is issued online after payment is accepted, all purchases of memberships are final. No refunds are allowed.
Online Ticket Purchase: No refunds are allowed on ticket purchases. For Blank Park Zoo General Admission tickets, the tickets are valid 365 days from the date of purchase. For single day event tickets, group sales tickets or concert tickets, the ticket is only valid on the day specified. For Night Eyes tickets, the ticket is valid for all days of that event that occurs in that two-week period.
Education Classes: No refunds are available on Blank Park Zoo education classes. Limited exchanging of weeks on Summer Safari classes may be available (subject to availability) if the class start date is greater than thirty days away.
SHIPPING POLICY:
In general, shipping for gift shop purchases occurs up to 48 hours from the time the order is placed and we receive credit card approval. There may be times when shipping will not occur until 72 hours after credit card approval. Please keep this in mind when selecting a shipping method.
Warranty and Liability Disclaimer
EXCEPT AS LIMITED BY LAW, THE BLANK PARK ZOO FOUNDATION, INC. MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WITH RESPECT TO ITS WEBSITE, OR ANY PORTION THEREOF, INCLUDING ANY WARRANTIES OF TITLE, NONINFRINGEMENT OF COPYRIGHT, TRADEMARK OR PATENT RIGHTS OF OTHERS, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS OR SUITABILITY FOR ANY PURPOSE. IN NO EVENT WILL THE BLANK PARK ZOO FOUNDATION, INC. BE LIABLE FOR ANY INJURY, LOSS, CLAIM, DAMAGE OR ANY INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING EITHER DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH ITS WEBSITE.
Waiver of Responsibility for Defective or Contaminated Materials
The Blank Park Zoo Foundation, Inc. disclaims responsibility for any errors or omissions, including technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. Furthermore, the Blank Park Zoo Foundation, Inc. cannot and does not guarantee or warrant that files made available for downloading will be free of “viruses”, “infections” or similar software contaminations, which may render the software useless or cause damage or destruction to user’s hardware, software or system(s). Users are responsible for implementing sufficient procedures and protections against possible damage. Use of the Blank Park Zoo Foundation, Inc.’s website and the Internet in general is at the user’s own risk.
User Rules
To maintain an efficient and effective site that addresses the needs and interests of its viewers, the following rules apply to the use of this site:
a. users may not post or transmit any message that is libelous, defamatory or obscene, or violates any other person’s copyrights, privacy rights, trademarks, trade secrets or rights in any confidential information;
b. users may not post or transmit any message, data, image or program with the intent to threaten the safety of others and/or with the effect of causing a reasonable person to perceive a threat to his or her safety;
c. users may not collect email addresses or other personal information for marketing or other purposes;
d. users acknowledge and agree that the Blank Park Zoo Foundation, Inc. may take appropriate action in order to prevent the misuse of the site to disseminate information, statements or materials that may be abusive, destructive, harmful or threatening to the safety of others or in order to comply with any law or regulation of any government entity;
e. users may not interfere with other users’ use of the site, including, but not limited to, the disruption of the normal flow or use of the service;
f. users may not post or transmit any contaminated or destructive files or gain unauthorized access to the site;
g. users may not use this site to advertise products or services; and
h. users hereby grant the Blank Park Zoo Foundation, Inc. a perpetual, worldwide, irrevocable license to use, reproduce, modify, publish, perform, display and distribute any posting, any portion of such posting and any derivative works created from such posting, in print, electronic and other media, by any means now known or developed in the future. The Blank Park Zoo Foundation, Inc. shall not be obligated to pay the posting party any royalties or other compensation for use of the posting.
USE OF MATERIALS
Users may download, print or transmit information from the site subject to the following:
a. the appropriate copyright notice must be affixed to each copy downloaded, transmitted or printed;
b. use of materials available from the site must be for personal or informational purposes only and in no instance may be used for commercial purposes;
c. materials available from this site may not be modified in any manner; and
d. no materials available from this site (including links from pages on other websites) can be used, copied or distributed separate from the accompanying text.
Choice of Law
These terms and conditions shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Iowa.
fb.us.3838287.04
9/26/2011
Follow the Zoo!
Follow the Zoo!
© 2020 Blank Park Zoo. All rights reserved.
